

DANIFI BABILONIA

Frontend Web Developer and Bilingual Customer Service Representative

About Me

As a Frontend Web Developer and Bilingual Customer Service Representative, I am excited to have extensive experience in customer service in a bilingual environment and skills in creating and designing impressive user interfaces. Additionally, I have the ability to solve problems and work effectively in a team to optimize the user experience on any project presented to me. I am ready to face any challenge with enthusiasm and help take your business to the next level.

Experience

2023 - Act. **Technical Support Specialist**

Kodland

As a part-time Technical Support Specialist, I diagnosed and resolved software and hardware issues, configured systems, documented customer inquiries, and provided timely feedback. My problem-solving skills, attention to detail, and ability to work independently and as part of a team contributed to my success in this role.

2022 - Act. Frontend Developer

Freelance

Creating responsive projects and layout of web pages using JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Bootstrap, Bootswatch and Redux and implementing backend structures with Node Js

2021 - 2023 **Bilingual Customer Service Representative**

Teleperformance

For over a year, I worked as a Bilingual Customer Service Representative in the Payments LÓB of eBay, where I acquired customer service skills in a bilingual environment and was able to develop my problem-solving and teamwork abilities.

Frontend Developer 2020 - 2021

Lovelace

I worked as a Frontend Developer at Lovelace, using React.js and Node.js. My responsibilities included creating and designing the user interface, making sure the application was functional and easy to use. I implemented user components, responsive layouts and managed user permissions, optimizing the user experience.

Contact Me

(+57) 301 405 6354 Medellin - Antioquia (Open to dantealigheri.1998@gmail.com

Additional Information:

Portfolio Web

https://danielbabilonia.netlify.app/

Education

Computer Systems and Engineering

Full Stack Web Developer

Lenguages





Spanish







Programming Skills

JavaScript











React IS





Node JS

References

Mauricio Maldonado Iturriago

Mauricio Andrés Pacheco Perez



DANIFI BABILONIA

Desarrollador Web Frontend y Representante de Servicio al cliente Bilingüe

Sobre Mi

Como Desarrollador Web Frontend y Representante de Servicio al Cliente Bilingüe, estoy emocionado de contar con una amplia experiencia en atención al cliente en un ambiente bilingüe y habilidades en la creación y diseño de interfaces de usuario impresionantes. Además, tengo la capacidad de solucionar problemas y trabajar en equipo de manera efectiva para optimizar la experiencia del usuario en cualquier provecto que se me presente.

Estoy listo para enfrentar cualquier desafío con entusiasmo y ayudar a llevar su negocio al siguiente nivel.

Experiencia

Technical Support Specialist 2023 - Act.

Como Especialista en Soporte Técnico, diagnosticaba y resolvía problemas de software y hardware, configuraba sistemas, documentaba consultas de clientes y proporcionaba comentarios oportunos. Mis habilidades para resolver problemas, atención al detalle y capacidad para trabajar de manera independiente y en equipo contribuyeron a mi éxito en este rol.

2022 - Act. **Desarrollo Frontend**

Freelance

Creación de proyectos responsive y maquetación de sitios web con JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React, Bootstrap, Bootswatch y Redux así como implementación de estructuras backend con Node Js v PSQL.

Representante de Servicio al Cliente 2021 - 2023 Bilingüe.

Teleperformance

Durante más de un año trabajé como Representante de Servicio al Cliente Bilingüe en el LOB de Payments de eBay, donde adquirí habilidades en atención al cliente en un ambiente bilingüe y pude desarrollar mi capacidad de solución de problemas y trabajo en equipo.

2020 - 2021 **Desarrollador Frontend**

Lovelace

Trabajé como desarrollador Frontend en Lovelace, utilizando React.is y Node.is. Mis responsabilidades incluyeron la creación y diseño de la interfaz de usuario, asegurándome de que la aplicación fuera funcional y fácil de usar. Implementé componentes de usuario, diseños responsivos y gestioné los permisos de usuario, optimizando la experiencia de usuario.

Contacto

(+57) 301 405 6354

Medellin - Antioquia (Abierto a cambios)

dantealigheri.1998@gmail.com

Additional Information:

Portfolio Web

https://danielbabilonia.netlify.app/

Educación

Ingenieria de Sistemas y Computacion

Desarollador Web FullStack

Idiomas

Inalés





Habilidades

JavaScript









PSQL



References

Mauricio Maldonado Iturriago

Mauricio Andrés Pacheco Perez